networkingphoenix.com 2017-03-23

# Privacy Policy

Welcome to NetworkingPhoenix.com . NetworkedLocal LLC and/or its affiliates (" networkingphoenix.com", "networkedchicago.com " or "Us") provide website features to you subject to the following privacy policy. 

NetworkingPhoenix.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. 

**By visiting NetworkingPhoenix.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

**What Personal Information About Customers Does NetworkingPhoenix.com Gather?**  
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at NetworkingPhoenix.com . Here are the types of information we gather. Please note that we are  **not**  in the business of selling, renting, or otherwise distributing your information to others.   

  * **Information You Give Us:** We reserve the right to receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way (we DO NOT store credit card information). You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing/enhancing future user experience for you, improving our user experience, and communicating with you.
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses NetworkingPhoenix.com or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of NetworkingPhoenix.com on other Web sites.
  * **E-mail Communications:** To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from NetworkingPhoenix.com if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your email settings in your [user account](https://www.networkingphoenix.com/user).
  * **Information from Other Sources:** We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

**What About Cookies?**  

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide personalized features for you, and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.
  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of NetworkingPhoenix.com's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any NetworkingPhoenix.com products and services that require you to Sign in. 

**Does NetworkingPhoenix.com Share the Information It Receives (ie. email addresses)?**  
In short... no, but some exceptions do apply. Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are **not** in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below and with subsidiaries we control that either are subject to this Privacy Policy or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy. 

  * **Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control:** We work closely with affiliated businesses. For example, the organizations who provide free event entry to our [Networking Passport](https://www.networkingphoenix.com/networking-passport/membership) subscribers. These organizations do have some access to customer information, but only under very specific conditions as described by the program's [terms and conditions](https://www.networkingphoenix.com/legal/networking-passport-tm-membership-terms-conditions).
  * **Third-Party Service Providers:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
  * **Promotional Offers:** Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of NetworkingPhoenix.com customers on behalf of other businesses through our "Alert" emails. When we do this, we do not share any user information with them. If you do not want to receive such offers, please adjust your email settings in your [user account](https://www.networkingphoenix.com/user).
  * **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that NetworkedLocal LLC, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
  * **Protection of NetworkingPhoenix.com and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our [Conditions of Use](https://www.networkingphoenix.com/help/conditions-of-use) and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of NetworkingPhoenix.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.
  * **With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**  

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
  * We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing through a Secure Socket.
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**What About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Websites?**  
Our site includes third-party advertising and links to other Web sites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party Web sites. 

**Which Information Can I Access?**  
NetworkingPhoenix.com gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with NetworkingPhoenix.com for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. 

**What Choices Do I Have?**  

  * As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such NetworkingPhoenix.com features as [Your Profile](https://www.networkingphoenix.com/user), Reviews, and [Networking Passport](https://www.networkingphoenix.com/networking-passport/membership). 
  * You can add or update certain information on pages such as your personal blog, or comment/reviews left by you.
  * If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your email settings in your [user account](https://www.networkingphoenix.com/user). (If you do not want to receive [Conditions of Use](https://www.networkingphoenix.com/help/conditions-of-use) and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those notices will still govern your use of NetworkingPhoenix.com, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.) 
  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of NetworkingPhoenix.com's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any NetworkingPhoenix.com products and services that require you to Sign in. 

**Are Children Allowed to Use NetworkingPhoenix.com?**  
NetworkingPhoenix.com does not sell products/services for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use NetworkingPhoenix.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**  
If you choose to visit NetworkingPhoenix.com , your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our [Conditions of Use](https://www.networkingphoenix.com/help/conditions-of-use) , including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Arizona. If you have any concern about privacy at NetworkingPhoenix.com [contact us](https://www.networkingphoenix.com/contact) with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Policy and the [Conditions of Use](https://www.networkingphoenix.com/help/conditions-of-use) will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers. 

**Automatic Information**  
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; events you viewed or searched for. We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our Web site for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.  Please note that we are  **not**  in the business of selling, renting, or otherwise distributing your information to others; the information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at NetworkingPhoenix.com . 

**Information Imported via Social Media**  
Social Media accounts/applications include, but are not limited to, the following: Facebook™, LinkedIn™;, GooglePlus™, Twitter™, Pinterest™, et al. For your convenience, you can create a NetworkingPhoenix.com account with your Social Media account credentials and/or simply link your NetworkingPhoenix.com account with Social Media accounts (taking advantage of seamless logins, sharing, etc). In doing so, you are explicitly agreeing to allow us to store your Social Media profile information for which you've given us access to via the NetworkingPhoenix.com Social Media application. Any data we retrieve and store through this method is directly integrated into our profile system and thus editable/deletable by you. Please note that we are  **not**  in the business of selling, renting, or otherwise distributing your information to others; the information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at NetworkingPhoenix.com . 

**Information from Other Sources**  
Examples of information we receive from other sources include page-view information from some merchants with which we operate co-branded businesses or for which we provide technical, advertising, or other services; Alexa Internet; search results and links.Please note that we are  **not**  in the business of selling, renting, or otherwise distributing your information to others; the information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at NetworkingPhoenix.com .
